[
  {
    "question": "Enter insured's date of birth",
    "action" : "CALANDER_ACTION",
    "Year" : "1999",
    "Month" : "FEB",
    "Day" : "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the insured's policy or certificate Number(s)?",
    "answer": "12345"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the insured's first name?",
    "answer" : "Automation"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the insured's middle initial?",
    "answer" : "test"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the insured's last name?",
    "answer" : "Testing"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the insured's Maiden Name (or other names they are known by)?",
    "answer" : "Maiden"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the insured's Social Security Number?",
    "answer" : "111-11-1111"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enter insured's date of death",
    "action" : "CALANDER_ACTION",
    "Year" : "2020",
    "Month" : "FEB",
    "Day" : "11"

  },
  {
    "question": "Select Cause of Death",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "Natural"

  },
  {
    "question": "Select Gender",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "Male"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Where is the insured Street Address?",
    "answer" : "Test"

  },
  {
    "question" : "In which City?",
    "answer" : "City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Select insured's State of residence",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "AL"

  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the insured's Zip code",
    "answer" : "12312"
  },
  {
    "question": "Was deceased receiving Medicaid?",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question" : "How much is the funeral bill amount?",
    "answer" : "111.11"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the funeral home's name?",
    "answer" : "HITE FUNERAL HOME"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the funeral home's tax ID number?",
    "answer" : "123142313"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Where is the Funeral Home Street Address?",
    "answer" : "address"
  },
  {
    "question" : "In which city?",
    "action" : "PREFILLED_DATA",
    "answer" : "test"
  },
  {
    "question" : "In which state?",
    "action" : "PREFILLED_DATA",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "answer" : "IN"

  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the funeral home's ZIP code?",
    "action" : "PREFILLED_DATA"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the funeral home's phone number?",
    "answer" : "12313131313"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the funeral home's fax number?",
    "answer" : "12345678904"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the funeral home's email address?",
    "answer" : "test@test.com"
  },
  {
    "question": "Select how benefit amount will be paid out",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "Check"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the beneficiary's full name?",
    "answer" : "Beneficiary Test"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the beneficiary's relationship to the insured?",
    "answer" : "test"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Where is the beneficiary residing?",
    "answer" : "test"
  },
  {
    "question" : "In which city?",
    "answer" : "test"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which state?",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "IN"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the beneficiary's ZIP code?",
    "answer" : "12345"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the beneficiary's Social Security Number?",
    "answer" : "111111111"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the beneficiary's email address?",
    "answer" : "test@test.com"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the beneficiary's phone number?",
    "answer" : "11111111111"
  },
  {
    "question": "Select how benefit amount will be paid to the beneficiary",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "Funeral home to deliver to the beneficiary"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Funeral Director's Printed Name",
    "answer" : "Test"
  },
  {
    "question": "Signature of Funeral Director",
    "action" : "SIGNATURE_ACTION",
    "value" : "signatureHelper"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Can beneficiary or next of kin sign the claimant form?",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Next of Kin or Beneficiary's Printed Name",
    "answer" : "test"
  },
  {
    "question": "Signature of Funeral Director",
    "action" : "SIGNATURE_ACTION",
    "value" : "signatureHelper"
  },
  {
    "question": "Upload Funeral Home Bill",
    "action" : "UPLOADDOCUMENT_ACTION",
    "value" : "uploadDocumentHelper"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would you like to be contacted by a Unity Customer Service Representative in order to build a stronger relationship with Unity and our products?",
    "action" : "DROPDOWN_ACTION",
    "value" : "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Where is the insured Street Address?",
    "action" : "PREFILLED_DATA"

  }
]